Life: Some disassembly required.
Demolition is a comedy, drama film directed by Jean-Marc Vallée.
An emotionally desperate investment banker finds hope through a woman he meets.
Davis Mitchell, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Karen Moreno, played by Naomi Watts.
Phil Eastwood, played by Chris Cooper.
Chris Moreno, played by Judah Lewis.
Carl, played by C.J. Wilson.
Margot Eastwood, played by Polly Draper.
Demolition is a 2015 American comedy-drama film directed by
Jean-Marc Vallée and written by Bryan Sipe.
The film stars Jake Gyllenhaal, Naomi Watts, Chris Cooper, and Judah Lewis.
The film opened the 2015 Toronto International Film Festival and was
theatrically released on April 8, 2016, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
The film explores themes of infidelity, new york city,
loss of loved one, pregnancy, dark comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.